Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Can I have a sip of water. please?
[sighs loudly]
I cannot begrudge you taking
pleasure in a petty victory.
After all. when should you give
anything away for free in this world?
I'll tell you what.
I'll pay you for a sip of water.
$50.000.
You're not paying anyone shit.
Well. that's my offer.
You're welcome to decline.
but then I'll have to kill you.
What's your name?
Why?
I just want to know the name of the
first man I'll kill with my own hands.
Shut the fuck up.
Okay
[tires screeching]
[shots fired]
Abel.
Sweetheart. my nectar.
So nice to see you. baby.
Do you bring me the cash?
Of course.
You see this?
$50.000.
You thought it was going
to be bigger?
Nah. this stack of papers
isn't that impressive at all.
But I think it would have been
a fair price for a sip of water.
I brought you something.
Oh. you are very thoughtful.
Mm-hmm.
Oh. no. no. no.
No. Abel.
What?
Not the head.
Why not?
It's too quick.
OK.
Stomach.
Death assured.
but it takes much longer.
Very painful.
What's your name?
Alex.
OK.
Thanks for the water. Alex.
No. wait. wait. wait.
wait. wait. wait.
[shot fired]
[loud thud]
I have a surprise for you.
You know I hate surprises.
You're not going
to hate this one.
I found him.
Mason Goddard.
Who else?
I've been waiting for this day.
Thank you.
Let's go!
What a shithole.
You hate golf.
What. you're a golfer now?
Well. it's my new hobby.
All by yourself?
Where is everybody?
Well. to be honest. they wouldn't
allow me to be a member. so I bought it.
Now I'm the only member.
Something about my
background check confused them.
You're a crazy motherfucker.
I love you.
Man.
you're not an easy guy to find.
Yeah. it's almost like I
wanted to be left alone. isn't it?
Well. you're not alone anymore.
Huh?
No. I'm not.
Come on. give me a tour.
-I want to see this place.
-Alright
It feels so appealing
Could dance on the ceiling
Whistling a sweet serenade
Oh. boy
What?
This looks like the place
of a guy who got dumped.
Amy did not dump me.
Amy and I are just
taking a break. that's all.
Come on. Mason.
I'm your little brother.
You can't bullshit me.
It's all right.
It's over.
Cheers.
Oh. cheer.
Oh. that's a good toast.
Cheers to us breaking up.
Come on.
We need to get you
back on your feet. Mason.
No.
No?
Nope.
Just no?
No.
Come on.
We need
to get you out of the house. buddy.
Why?
Let me take you on a vacation.
I don't need a vacation.
I got all this!
This?
Yeah.
I play 18 holes of golf.
I come back.
I have a nice drink.
I watch some TV.
It's good.
This place is fucking
depressing. bro.
Oh. come on.
This is brutal.
Are you kidding me?
This is where you want
to stay here?
Feature zone. Sean.
This is old school. man.
This is. you know. country club. dark
green. you know. whiskey. Saturday night.
All right. fine.
Look.
At least let me take you
out for a drink or something.
You go out.
You go get a drink.
I'm fine here.
Oh. boy.
We got a whole bar here.
Fine. fine.
We'll stay here.
We'll just stay in.
I don't mind.
So how have you been?
Yeah. I'm good.
It's been. you know.
wasting time.
All right.
How about a game of chess?
Yeah. yeah. I can do that.
Let's do that.
I got a yes. huh?
Yeah.
Okay. but how about this?
If I win. then you let
me take you on vacation.
You have never won
against me at chess.
You never know.
It can happen.
Okay.
And if I win. you get the fuck
out of here and leave me alone.
Deal?
Fine.
Okay. good.
Deal.
Good.
Let's go.
All right.
Well. what do the
little horsies do again?
Well. that's a knight.
And remember.
it moves in an L shape.
Right. right.
I taught you that when
you were eight.
Okay.
I heard Decker's been doing
freelance bounty hunter work lately.
Oh yeah?
I'm sure she's good at it.
She's good at everything.
Oh. my boy.
You need to snap out
of it. buddy.
I mean. it's over. okay?
Look. I love Decker.
I just can't ever quite forget the fact
that she tried to put us all in prison.
That was her job. man.
Yeah. that's the problem. is you
and me. we're made to steal stuff.
Her. she was made
to put guys like us away.
It's not gonna happen. Sean.
I'm retired.
That's it.
Well. then you're
gonna love this vacation.
Checkmate.
What?
How did you do that?
What did you do?
Did you switch somebody around?
Show me what that move was.
What did you do before that?
I was here. and I went here.
Look.
You have nowhere to go.
Bitch!
You've been practicing.
I've had a lot
of time on my hands.
Oh. so you hustled me.
No. no. no.
We do this over again. because I didn't
know about the practicing and the hustling.
We'll do it over again.
It's a deal's a deal.
We made a bet.
I won.
Time to pack your bags.
It's only a vacation?
For real?
Yeah. a vacation.
No bullshit?
It's a vacation.
I got it all set up.
It's gonna be beautiful.
Okay. where are we going?
Miami.
Miami?
I like Miami.
Mason!
Mason
I missed you so much.
I missed you. too.
Are you taking care
of this bride?
Oh. yeah.
I just do whatever she tells me
to do.
Hey.
Victor. great to see you.
Looking good. brother.
Yes. sir.
Looking even better now. boss.
We got you back.
I love seeing
the family together.
I'm just glad to be here. guys.
Hey. who's ready to hit Miami?
I am.
Let's get it.
Let's go.
Why Miami?
Oh. they got baddies.
Great beaches. too.
Great clubs.
Great food.
Oh. and I got a special surprise
for us as soon as we touch down.
Yeah.
See?
None of you guys
thought I could pull this off.
And look where we are. huh?
All part of my plan. 3D chess.
I think you mean 4D chess.
3D chess is already
what chess is.
You're thinking about a man with a
plan three moves ahead of your opponent.
That's 4D.
Okay. see. did I not know that. or
did I just pretend not to know that?
That's deep. dude.
That's what I'm saying.
All right. let's go.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Miami!
Boy. I don't like the
look on your face.
It's just. I'm a little worried.
I know. because you know that Sean
has something planned. doesn't he?
I don't know exactly.
Well. how could you predict
what a 4D chess player's thinking?
You can't.
Listen. as soon as we get to
Miami. I got this plug named Big Lou.
We got everything we need.
Cars. yachts. ladies.
lobsters. caviar.
Let's get it.
That's two.
Tables?
Tables.
Tables on us.
Matter of fact. I know
somebody that's performing now.
Baddies?
Baddies on deck.
Making trouble
in every city we go to.
I figure it's only right that we
burn some of this adrenaline up.
Right here on the track.
Big Money Lewis!
What's up?
Anton. welcome to Miami. brother.
How was that flight?
How you been?
You been good?
Good. man.
Blessed.
Meet the fam.
That's the family.
That means you're my family.
How y'all doing?
Meet the fam.
That's the boss man right there.
This is my dog. Mickey.
Whatever you need. automobiles. food.
yachts. lobsters. caviar. anything y'all
need. hotels. suites. penthouses.
houses on the water. cigar boats. cigars.
I mean. whatever you need.
If it's family. it's family.
Mickey. don't play yourself.
Make sure it's great.
Welcome to Miami.
You guys ready?
Let's go.
How you doing. man?
Man. you're blessed. man.
Blessed.
What you got there?
Porsche. $4 million.
Right there in the middle. 3.5.
That beautiful thing over there.
only 1.5.
Nice. right?
It's a bargain. man.
Yeah.
You know. we blessed.
Matter of fact. you
should get behind the
wheel. get with the crew.
and have a good time.
No. no. no.
I'm good.
Listen. man.
I heard some great things.
-Great stories.
-Yeah?
I respect you and
the streets love you.
Matter of fact. man. I got
some big business lined up.
Some great opportunities.
Mm-mmm
[engines reving]
That's what I'm trying
to tell you.
I want to talk to you
about some business.
No. no. man.
I told you I'm retired.
Did my brother talk
to you or something?
Me and your brother
are good friends.
Yeah. I see that.
You guys here for the auction?
The auction?
Yeah. the Cavendish
Foundation fine arts auction.
Fine arts auction?
Uh. yes. we are.
We love the arts.
We're collectors.
Oh. amazing.
I'm on the board.
Well. that's wonderful.
Well. why don't you share with this
gentleman some of your favorite artists?
Oh. uh. you know.
like the greats.
Michelangelo. Leonardo.
Raffaello. Donatello.
Uh-huh.
A Renaissance man.
Yes. yes.
Or a Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtle fan.
Here are your keys. sir.
Thank you very much.
You guys take care.
All right. you take care.
Hey. excuse me. miss.
If we were to want some nice
suits. do you have enough?
We don't need suits.
What if we did?
No. no. we don't need suits.
Well. you know.
we might want to dress up.
But we don't.
If we did?
Of course. we have an excellent in-house
tailor and also some personal shoppers.
We can take care of everything
for you.
Great.
What's your last name?
Trouble.
Wow.
How great is this place. huh?
That's nice.
Nice?
Are you kidding me?
This place is sick.
Why are we here. Sean?
Because we're on vacation.
Because you need this. Mason.
You need to get your mojo back.
Why are we here. Sean?
How many times are we going
to do this?
As many times as it takes.
Say it.
For... Say it.
We're here for a...
We're here for an art heist.
I'm sorry
for the smoke and mirrors.
I just knew you'd say no.
But why would I say no. Sean?
Because you always
say no to my ideas.
Sean. you don't need the money.
Your cut of the last crypto
wallet was 80 million.
I mean. you couldn't
possibly run out of cash.
No. don't.
Oh. fuck.
I may have made
a few bad investments.
I guess you did. didn't you?
Come on. that's the
name of the game. right?
Go big or go home.
Take that yacht there.
for example.
You think the guy who
owns that yacht plays it safe?
Hell no.
His name is Hamish Hawks.
and he's a fucking baller.
And how do you know that?
Because that's
who we're going to rob.
He's a big shot art guy.
He's got a painting at
the auction valued at over
$100 million. and it's
being stored on that yacht.
All we do is swoop in. grab
the painting. and then we vanish.
Who hired you?
His ex-wife.
She fucking hates him.
She already wired me a
million for expenses. and
then 50 more as soon as
we hand the painting over.
That's $8 million each.
I could wire you $8 million.
Come on.
I'm not going
to take your money. man.
The answer is no.
And how many times do I have to tell
you the jobs that look easy are never easy?
It's not going to happen.
Sorry.
But I'll tell you what
we are going to do.
We are going to enjoy ourselves
with this lovely resort. with
our friends. and then we're
going to go our separate ways.
That's it.
End of story.
Mason.
No. no.
Hold on a minute. bro.
You sure?
How fast?
Fast like Tyreek Hill?
Yeah. maybe faster.
Let me see.
Let's get it.
Listen. asshole.
All you do is give me excuses.
Every fucking day I'm
here fixing your shit.
paying you for years
and years and years.
I don't want to hear your
fucking bullshit anymore.
I don't care what
the fucking problem is.
Fix this shit now!
Looks like she's ready. boss.
Nah. nah. she's just
fed up with her boyfriend.
Pisses me off.
How you doing. man?
You know me. man.
Keeping busy.
staying out the way.
What are you up to?
What are you doing
with your free time?
I gave some of that crypto money to
build a community center back home.
You did not.
Yes. sir.
Are you kidding?
It's also a place where
kids can come to get
tutoring. mentorship.
and some street smarts.
Holy shit. man.
I'm impressed.
I'm so proud of you. man.
I'm even
coaching Pop Warner football. too.
Come on.
You're doing that?
I think I found the
secret recipe to success.
Is it secret or you can tell me?
All I do is gamble $100
each every game I win.
And now we undefeated.
Cheers to that.
Man. that is awesome.
You're inspiring me now.
Go ahead. take one card.
Number one.
ace of clubs. remember?
Perfect. perfect.
Thank you. thank you.
thank you very much.
Remember from the
bottom is ace of spades.
On the bottom. go ahead.
turn over those cards.
I'm going to ask you to
name your card in a second.
What's the name of your card?
How did you do that?
No. I'm still pissed off.
He's never won.
I taught him how to
play chess. and suddenly
out of nowhere... Good
evening. everyone.
Hope you're
having a magical night.
Would you mind taking a card?
Why not?
I'm just curious.
Can you make yourself disappear?
Well. as you wish.
Where'd he go?
Man. really disappeared.
Thanks
for getting rid of that guy.
Yeah. I got to track that guy
down. learn some of his tricks.
You know what?
I just want to say that I'm really
happy that we're all together.
It's. you know. it's having the
family back again. so it feels good.
I love you.
I love you. too.
Well. we've been through a lot.
Yeah.
Yeah. man. tell me about it.
I'm just bored all the time.
Are you?
Maybe you need a hobby. Victor.
What am I gonna do. golf?
It's for old people.
Yeah. maybe try some pickleball.
Now we're talking.
I would do that.
That's cool.
Whatever our future is. tonight.
let's just have a fucking good time.
Whoo!
Yeah!
Mmm.
What's going on here?
You have something
that you want to tell us?
I think you do.
You tell them. babe.
What?
What's going on?
Say it.
What?
Yeah. we haven't told anyone
yet because it's still early.
but I think you guys should
be the first one to know.
I'm pregnant.
Oh. no way.
Congratulations.
Congrats. guys.
Wow. this is amazing.
Well. you know we're
going to be the godfather.
Hey. hey. hey. I'm not changing
any diapers. just so you guys know.
I mean...
Cheers to the baby.
-Cheers!
-Thank you.
No. you're not getting
any dessert.
Come on. babe.
I just wanted a piece of cake.
We've gone over this.
You're getting... That's him.
Who?
It's Hamish Hawks. the
guy who owns the yacht.
We've had these
conversations numerous times.
Yeah.
you see that watch on his wrist?
It's an RM-56.
worth 1.6 million.
Oh. okay.
I think I'll just go say hi.
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry for interrupting.
Are you Mr. Hawks?
I'm Mason Goddard.
Nice to meet you.
I hear that you have the
most fabulous art collection.
Is that true?
Of course.
Everybody knows that.
May I ask you a question?
Why do you collect art?
It's good business.
Yes. yes.
But do you ever look
at your art?
Do you ever appreciate
the art that you do have?
What's your deal?
I'm just curious.
Okay. Mr. Curious Type.
My art collection?
It's like money sitting
in the bank.
Ah. I see. I see.
Well. I may be overstepping my
bounds. but a piece of advice for you.
I would really appreciate
what you have. my
friend. because you
could lose it like that.
Trust me. I've been there.
I've lost a lot.
Let me tell you something.
I don't take advice.
And I'm not your friend.
Absolutely.
So. bonsoir.
Bonsoir.
Have a good evening.
Good evening to you.
Okay.
Au revoir.
What was that all about?
Oh.
Yeah.
I think I reacted hastily.
dismissing your plan.
-Really?
-Yeah
No shit
Let's have some fun.
Yeah. let's do it.
I'm gonna take a walk.
I'll be back.
Odessa.
Mason.
Nice sleight of hand.
by the way.
I see you haven't lost
your touch.
You caught that?
I don't miss much.
You haven't changed much either.
What the fuck?
Where's my watch?
Want to take a stroll?
Sure.
So. what brings you to Miami?
So I'm dragged in here.
On a job?
No. no. I'm retired.
If you say so. Mason.
I'll play along.
What about you?
What about me?
Well. one of the world's
greatest art thieves
just happens to be at
a big fancy art auction.
What do you mean. one of?
Well. my bad. the best.
Was the best.
I've gone legit.
Come on.
Really?
Now I'm a consultant
for collectors.
In all my years. I became an
expert at what I was stealing.
Well. how much it was worth.
who the important buyers
are. and how far they'll
go. the one up to each other.
Bet they go pretty far. huh?
Oh. yeah.
I've got a room here for the duration of
the auction. but I actually live here now.
Really?
I found a great loft downtown.
Oh. that's nice.
You should come see
her for yourself sometime.
Just may do that.
Oh.
Yeah.
So?
You miss it?
What?
The game.
Do you?
Mm.
I'm going to take that as a yes.
So are you still involved with
that
Pretty little narc.
Decker
She's FBI.
That's what I said. a narc.
You are too much.
Yeah. well. anyway. we've gone
our separate ways. and it's fine.
And I'm good.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Are you really?
No. not really.
-No. I didn't think so.
-[both laugh]
Well. you know. I never
approved of you falling
in love with someone
from the other side.
But I am sorry if she hurt you.
Thank you.
You know. just because I've gone legit
doesn't mean I don't still know people.
I can make a call. make that
pretty little narc disappear.
Oh. yes.
Well. this has been
a pleasant surprise.
Yeah?
And anyway.
I hope you enjoy your vacation.
I'll try.
Well. if it turns into more than
that. it's none of my business.
I'm not a narc.
But if I should find out that
any of my clients' interests are
compromised because of your
vacation. well. then the gloves come off.
Totally fair. I wouldn't
expect anything less.
[Odessa chuckles]
Good night. Mason.
Good night.
I dug up the original blueprints
for the design of the yacht.
It's got all kinds of custom
perks. even a sex dungeon.
Really?
Yeah.
Where is it?
Right here
No kidding.
Got to kill time at sea somehow. right?
And over here. there is a
trash room on the bottom level.
It's refrigerated to keep garbage
from rotting and smelling up the ship.
Yeah. but that's standard.
and collectors do like
to keep their art in the
climate-controlled rooms.
Okay.
so that's where it could be.
It could be.
Uh-huh.
But it's trash.
They say one man's art
is another man's trash.
Think about it.
Well. thank you. Sean.
That was great.
Yeah.
You know. you and Odessa
looked good together last night.
Oh. yeah?
I can see why you
almost married that girl.
Yeah.
She's like your first Decker.
She's always
been pretty special.
Hey. you know what?
Why don't we just
steal the whole yacht?
Are you kidding?
You know how fast that goes?
About 30 miles an hour.
It'd be the slowest. most embarrassing
chase that you've ever seen.
See?
This is why I need you. Mason.
Yeah. well. you got me.
I just got to figure things
out before tomorrow.
And I need to get some supplies
from my local guy. like our wetsuits.
No. no. not for me.
You guys do that.
Are you sure?
I'm not going in the water.
Come on.
It's like tradition there.
No. no.
Let's go over there.
Tomorrow's the auction.
We got to move.
Hey. look who it is.
Mr. Curious type. right?
Hey. guilty as charged.
Guilty?
Funny you say that.
Last time we met. I seemed
to have lost my watch.
Really?
Did you check the lost
and found?
I'm sure a lovely
hotel like this has one.
You know. maybe you
should ask around about me.
Art. it's not the
only thing I collect.
I bet.
I bet that you have a
hell of a stamp collection.
No.
I think I'm starting
to like this guy.
You do.
Let's go talk.
Come on.
Here's to a fair fight.
Let's try to avoid getting into
another bidding war. Mrs. Cavendish.
I make no promises.
I've already seen several
pieces that I really like.
You nearly bankrupted
me last year.
I know.
And it may happen
again this year.
And that's part of the fun.
That's the game.
I guess you're right.
Show no mercy.
No risk. no reward.
Exactly.
You in. babe?
Of course I'm in. babe.
I already disabled the
security cameras on the
yacht. and now I got
eyes on the whole resort.
How do I look?
Hot.
Who are you talking to?
Um. I was just... praying.
Aw. that's so sweet.
I do that too.
Tell her if she doesn't
take her hand off you.
I'm probably gonna
come down and chop it off.
God bless you.
Okay.
I don't know how many times
I need to fucking tell you this.
Don't fuck with me.
You're wasting my fucking time.
I don't give a fuck.
I'm gonna start charging
you by the second now.
You understand?
Anton. tie him up.
Hamish is going to
lose more than a painting
tonight if he doesn't
start treating his lady right.
Copy that.
I think she'd make a
great girlfriend. Sean.
Hey. you think I got a shot?
Definitely.
Anton and Victor are
in place on the yacht.
Copy that.
I feel like it looks like I'm your
assistant again. like on the casino heist.
Yeah.
that's what it should look like.
Well. next time. I want to be the big
shot. and you look like my assistant.
All right.
Anything you say.
Really?
Yeah.
Considering there
won't be a next time.
Keep telling yourself that.
Okay.
The guards are under control.
You hear that?
I did.
See?
What did I tell you?
Easy money.
Please don't say that.
Tanner. Mace.
I repeat. do you copy?
Are you Ralph?
Hamish told us
we could see you here.
What do you want?
A ride.
You're on the fucking ground.
Hey. listen. man.
You don't want to do this.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm the one with the gun.
Get on the couch.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
You think I'm fucking around?
You two.
put your bitch ass down.
Tie them up now.
Tie them now.
Slow as hell.
Stop moving.
Don't fucking move.
Hello. Caras.
Agent Richter.
Get the fuck down.
Nice suit. boss.
Thanks.
Lead the way
Come on.
This way.
Here for the auction?
Yeah.
The auction.
So you're a collector now?
I dabble
Well.
you certainly can afford it.
What about you. Agent Richter?
Why are you here?
I'm just here on vacation.
Bullshit.
Vacation?
Wow.
Federal employees spend
more money than I thought.
Not as much as bank
managers turn criminals.
But some of us do okay.
Criminal?
Those days are long gone.
I'm glad to hear it.
I recommend you keep
it that way.
What is this?
Link.
we're in a fucking wine room.
It's supposed
to be a trash room.
What's happening?
I don't know.
Maybe they did further
renovations I didn't know about.
It's gotta be there somewhere.
Mason. do you copy?
I muted the others so they don't
get nervous. but Richter's here.
Richter?
Where the fuck is Richter?
At the gala.
What?
Yeah.
Okay have Caras keep his eyes
on him.
Don't let him take his eyes
off him.
This must be it.
Mason. tell me we have a plan B. If I
have a plan B. you'll be the first to know.
Mason?
Yeah. bring it out.
Bring it out.
Is that it?
Yeah. yeah.
Let's do it.
Wait. wait. wait.
Agent Richter?
As in FBI Agent Richter?
Yes. he's at the gala.
Still have eyes on Richter.
What's he doing?
It looks like he's
about to get laid.
Oh. gross.
Something's wrong.
Just doesn't add up.
Oh. come on.
There it is.
Turn around.
Slide it.
Come on. slide it.
I got it. boss.
Take it.
Bye. guys.
I'm so sorry about this.
We'll be out
of here in a minute.
Just sit tight.
OK. let's go.
Go. go. go.
Anton. up. up. growing.
Guys. the wind is picking up.
See?
Easy money.
Too easy.
Something's wrong.
Doesn't make sense.
Yeah. you know what else doesn't make
sense is all those explosives on the boat.
Explosives?
What are you talking about. explosives?
Well. there was a
bunch of C4 on the bus.
Where?
Fuck!
OK. have Caras not take his
fucking eyes off of him. OK?
What?
Mason.
I was trying to tell you.
You sons. we've got to
get off this boat fucking now.
You got it.
[huge explosion in distance]
Wow.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's so nice.
I love this time of year.
Yeah.
Salud.
Pardon.
It's done.
Mason is dead.
How does it feel. Abel?
A little anticlimactic.
Maybe I should have
made him suffer more.
And make him a martyr
in the criminal community.
not after everything
he put you through.
As usual. you make a good point.
Mason Goddard. once the
most respected thief in the
game. outwitted by the most
dangerous man in the world.
That's the headline.
I'm not all that dangerous.
I know that. baby.
But image is everything.
Now maybe we can have some peace
and quiet for a while. huh?
I like the sound of that.
[phone buzzing]
Excuse me.
Hamish. well done.
My pleasure.
I didn't know that Mason guy for long.
but he's starting to get on my nerves.
I only wish I could have been
there myself to see the fireworks.
You and I still have
some business to discuss.
Not now.
Tonight is for celebrating.
Maybe for you. but not for me.
I said not now. Hamish.
The only reason I decided
to help you is because you
finally agreed to cough
up the money you owed me.
Don't make me
repeat myself again.
Not everyone's scared of you.
You sure?
I was just informed by
a very reliable source
that I am the most
dangerous man in the world.
Abel!
My yacht is headed up this way.
I trust you and Violet will pack your
bags and disembark before it does so.
Salud.
Baby
To you.
Well. so much for you
not getting in the water.
Don't say it.
Not getting in the water.
And he said it.
Explosives?
What are you talking about. explosives?
I was trying to tell you.
We've got to get off
this boat fucking now.
Come on.
Damn. man.
this water's cold as hell.
Fuck this bullshit.
No. no. you guys can't
complain about anything.
I'm the one without a hoods.
Hey. what about me?
No. no. you. you don't get to
complain about anything ever again.
Get us into this mess.
Okay. pick it up.
Let's go.
You're the one
who didn't want to wetsuit.
Shut up.
This shit is heavy.
Well. shit.
at least we got the painting.
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
Mason?
It's Mason.
They're alive.
How?
Where are you guys?
We're going to be right there.
I'm too old for this. Sean.
Come on.
Bring it.
Oh my god. you guys.
We thought you were dead.
Let's go.
I knew you guys would
make it out somehow.
Hold it man!
Let's get the fuck out of here!
Move it out
We brought you some clothes. guys.
Fuck
Hell yeah!
Mason.
After that explosion. I just
didn't know if... Come on. you
didn't think I had anything to
do with that explosion. did you?
Oh.
Sean. hi.
Good to see you. Odessa.
Sorry to barge in like
this. but are you busy?
No. no. no. come on in.
It's more than just us. though.
Oh. all right.
Gang's all here.
Still okay?
Very good.
-Come on.
-Thank you
Hey.
Uh-huh
Come on in.
We need your opinion
on something.
Interesting way to spend
your vacation. I see.
This one's not on me.
It was my fault. as usual.
But I think we have something
pretty special on the hands.
Exciting.
So?
Silent Beauty by Winston Penn.
Currently valued just
north of $100 million.
$100 million?
Woo!
Ok.
Nicely done. Sean.
You're tight too. huh?
Let's put it over here.
What kind of a fucking idiot would
spend $100 million on this shit?
This is ugly as fuck.
I don't know.
I mean. it sure look good to me.
Careful.
I know my methods might be a little crazy
sometimes. but your boy Sean gets it done.
Yes. sir.
4D chess. Mason.
Oh. it's impressive.
See?
My girl Odessa gets it.
Let her finish.
Yeah.
Very impressive.
Impressive... forgery.
What?
Wait. you gotta be shitting me.
No. I don't.
Sean!
Don't be shitting me.
No. it can't be.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Look at it. Sean.
It's too perfect.
See this?
Take a look
at this section right there.
You see that?
In the original painting. you could
see tiny little cracks in the oil paint.
Come. take a look.
See that?
Tough break. Sean.
Yeah. man.
Yep.
Put it. a tough break.
Hold on.
So you mean to tell me we almost
got blown up over a fake painting?
I knew it.
When that boat blew
up. I knew it was a forger.
You did?
Yes. yes.
That was the plan all the time.
Don't you get it?
They wanted to blow us up
and the painting and then collect.
Who would benefit
from collecting on this?
Who?
The owner of the painting.
That's right.
It's an insurance scam.
Bingo.
Gotta admit.
it's not a bad scheme.
I think I get it.
Hey. why don't you spell it
out for us dumb fucks then?
It's simple.
Someone buys
an original painting.
They insure it.
And if it gets destroyed or
soiled or lost. full recovery.
You collect everything back.
All while secretly holding
on to the original painting.
Yeah. I gotta admit.
that's pretty smart.
No. it's not that fucking smart.
If the plan worked and the
word got out. that fuckboy
Hamish would be on the
hook for four counts of murder.
You talking about Hamish Hawks?
Yeah.
He. uh. he owns the painting.
Hamish Hawks doesn't own
Silent Beauty.
You sure?
It was on his yacht.
That's not Hamish's yacht.
It belongs to one of
his business associates.
No. no. no.
That's why Richter's here.
Hell fucking no.
Please don't say what I
think you're about to say.
Salzar owns the painting
and the yacht.
Is that right?
Well. technically. the
painting and the yacht
are listed under a couple
of his shell companies.
But yeah. Mason. you're right.
It's Salsar.
How can you be so sure?
Because I'm the one that brokered the
deal back when he bought the painting.
Abel Salzar is my client.
Oh.
Oh. shit.
Oh. hell no.
Can I try some?
No.
You have your own ice cream.
Whatever.
What's the matter.
Agent Richter?
No ice cream for you?
I'm lactose intolerant.
You don't seem surprised
to see me.
You don't really think I thought
that you were killed in an explosion.
You played that trick before.
Well. this one's not on me. man.
Maybe it was Decker trying
to put you out of your misery.
I tell you. I'm sorry to
hear the two of you broke
up. but I could have
told you a long time ago.
It was never gonna last.
Well. you didn't.
I'm always the last to know.
aren't I?
You think maybe I have a chance
with her?
You love to see me in
a tight spot. don't you?
I'd say I'm entitled
to gloat a little.
How many times have I
had to chase you in the past?
Now you're coming to me.
I would have appreciated
a heads-up once also.
Now. why would I do that?
I can just trail
your crew instead.
Oh. so you admit it.
that you use us as bait.
I admit to being good
at what I do.
So where is he?
Where's Salzar?
Hm?
You don't know. do you?
Oh. my god.
You almost get us killed. and
you don't even know where he is.
Maybe you're not as
good as you say you are.
Yeah. well. he's not an idiot.
And I know he's
around here somewhere.
But he uses proxies
for everything.
His proxies have proxies.
The man's a ghost.
And now he thinks I'm a ghost. so.
Well. lucky for you.
No. unlucky for him.
I'm tired of this shit.
We've gotten him before.
We'll get him again.
What are you saying?
You have a plan?
I do.
I think I do.
Tell me more.
I think that was the best
pasta I've ever tasted.
No. really
Well. thank you.
How do you do that?
Well. actually. I used to go out with
one of the biggest chefs in the world.
You've seen him on TV.
And I picked up a few skills.
That makes sense.
Before. I caught him in bed with
an Academy Award
winning actress.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm enjoying taking time just
for myself.
You know?
It can get lonely. but everybody
gets a little lonely sometimes.
Probably even someone
like Abel Salazar.
How long have you been working
with him?
Well. his people used to buy some of
the art I stole back when I was a thief.
And once I went legit. I did
some business with Hamish.
but then I realized that
Hamish was just the middleman.
Salazar was the real buyer.
Eventually. Abel came to trust
me enough to work with me directly.
You should be careful with him.
I know he's suave and sophisticated
and all that. but he's a bad man.
I can take care of myself.
I know you can.
I just wouldn't want to see
anything happen to you. that's all.
Why?
Because I care.
I care about you.
Mason.
We should talk more
about this plan.
The plan. Mason?
We've gone
over it half a dozen times.
Yeah. but we don't have a
plan B. and that's important.
With a plan A that's good. you don't
need a plan B. I don't know about that.
Mason. we've got this.
Okay. well.
I should go check on the crew.
Make sure that Sean
doesn't get in trouble.
He's lucky to have you.
They all are.
I feel the same way about them.
You know. they drive me a
little crazy. but I feel happy.
Family.
Good night.
Good night. Mace.
French way.
Oh. my God.
So decadent.
I love it.
You finish it.
I'm stuffed.
Oh. are you sure I'm not
getting too much sugar?
That was a pretty good line. huh?
You're very convincing baby.
It's what I do.
I knew he didn't like
bullies. so I played the bully.
It gave him a little bit more
incentive to want to steal from me.
Or at least to think it was
you he was stealing from.
That's right.
I knew he wouldn't be able
to resist.
Well. you are irresistible.
Even more so than this cake.
Hey.
How was dinner?
It was good.
Yeah. I told Odessa it was
the best pasta I ever had.
Some sort of. like. lobster.
scallops. and. like. a fettuccine type.
It was good.
You know. she still likes you.
She didn't invite any of
the rest of us to dinner.
Well. that's because
we had to make a plan.
Sure. the plan.
Mm-hmm.
Do you trust her?
Yeah.
Yeah. I do.
Good.
You know. it's... it's okay.
What's okay?
I mean. not to sound cheesy about it. but.
like. it's okay to open your heart back up.
Uh...
My sweet brother.
Wow.
You're a good man.
So are you. Mason.
Yeah.
It's getting cold out here.
You come back inside?
No. I'm gonna wait
till the roaches vacate.
Then I'll go back in.
Yeah. this is definitely a step
down from that resort. huh?
Odessa. how did the auction go?
Excellent.
I got you every piece
you wanted.
Of course you did.
That's why I pay you so well.
I'll have them all
delivered to you tomorrow.
And I was thinking I might make the
drive up and see you and Hector as well.
Oh. and to what would we owe
that honor?
I have a surprise for you.
What is it with women
and surprises?
It's about Mason Goddard.
Yes. I know.
Mason Goddard. he's dead.
He's fish food.
No. Abel.
Mason is alive.
And he's going to make
a move against you.
And I know exactly
what he's planning to do.
Please open your trunk. ma'am.
Sure.
We're clear.
Welcome. ma'am.
Thank you.
The truck with the new
artwork will be following shortly.
All right. thanks.
I'm going to have to frisk you.
Well. have at it. handsome.
Although I don't know
where I'd be hiding anything.
That won't be necessary.
Odessa will never hurt me. because
that would be very bad for business.
I might try to steal from you.
Oh. my god.
Your commissions on these deals
are already grand larceny. my dear.
You know I'm worth it.
Oh. you definitely are.
So you noticed the new
landscaping. right?
Well. yeah.
I did. You have like...
A park in front of your house.
It's beautiful. right?
Yeah.
So. what do you think?
Oh. cute little place
you got here. Abel.
My humble abode.
Where's the restroom?
Right down the hall on the left.
Thank you.
I'll wait
for you in the brain room.
All right.
Bold move to so prominently display a
supposedly destroyed work of art. Abel.
Your collection has grown.
Yeah.
Interesting.
That is Alex.
You name your guns?
Well. that one has a
special meaning to me.
You consider this a piece
of art?
Why not?
But don't touch it.
because that is a real gun.
Is it loaded?
Of course it is.
An unloaded weapon
is like a blank canvas.
Useful to the artist. but of
no use to a collector like me.
Can I offer you champagne?
Well. I never say no to bubbly.
Nectar. Odessa is here.
Odessa.
Hello.
Love the outfit.
Oh. right back at you.
So good to see you.
Yeah?
You look amazing.
How are you?
Everything's wonderful.
Good.
So happy we... I know.
we did it.
Sweetheart. right on time.
So. what are we celebrating?
Well. to fine art.
I like that.
Here's to owning art the
whole world thinks has been lost.
How about...
to owning the entire world.
Salud.
Cheers.
We've been expecting you.
Clear!
Sean got caught before
I could pick him up.
Damn it.
Be careful. babe.
Gentlemen. please
unload the crates over here.
And give them a hand. please.
Right over here. please.
This is exciting.
A gift from me to you. Abel.
Abel does not like surprises.
Well. this is no surprise.
Nectar.
Odessa gave me
a heads-up last night.
Oh?
What is it?
Open it!
Bravo!
Just like Lazarus. Mason
God arises from the dead.
How?
Well. vermin are notoriously
difficult to exterminate.
Yeah.
it can be hard to kill a rat.
Mm-hmm.
Well. maybe this was
meant to be. baby.
You regretted Mason
didn't suffer more?
Well. that's right.
Now we have the chance
to fix that.
You know.
Mason and I go way back.
We once even competed to steal
the same Giacometti sculpture.
And he won that little game.
But now I win
a much bigger game.
Really?
I was just a game to you. huh.
Odessa?
He thought that I would
help him steal from you.
Oh.
So what was the plan?
Sneak into my villa. make
away with some of my
valuables. and what.
drive off into the sunset?
Well. when you say it like that.
it sounds pretty simple. but...
Yeah. I guess that was the plan.
You trust her?
Thanks. Odessa.
Best gift ever.
Well. to be fair. it is a gift I
expect to be compensated for.
Oh. you will be. I promise.
Just curious. Odessa. how
much is my life worth to you?
What's the number?
Probably not as
much as you think.
Did you really think I was going
to let you rip off my biggest client?
Because once upon a time. you
used to mean something to me.
Yeah. I guess I did.
[Odessa laughs]
First Decker. now this.
You have terrible luck
with women. Mason.
Maybe I do.
And I almost feel sorry for you.
I guess it's a...
-There's always plan B.
-Plan B?
[loud explosion]
Where is he?
No. no. no. no. no. no.
Go find him!
You ready. babe?
On your word. honey.
Now!
Fire in the hole.
[loud explosion]
Son of a bitch.
It's okay. baby.
Hey. it's okay.
Somebody's gonna pay for this.
It's okay.
Move.
Move?
Jeez.
You need to chill out. bro.
Maybe you should try
some CBD gummies.
Maybe you should stay off
yachts where you're not welcome.
What the fuck. Odessa?
Hey. I did my part.
I delivered him to you.
I'm not the one
who let him get away.
You can always get
another yacht. baby.
Maybe even a bigger one.
Hey. this is the guy
who blew up your yacht.
Where's Mason?
I don't know. sir.
Then go find him!
Why the fuck would
you blow up my yacht?
Oh. my God.
You still haven't
figured it out. have you?
Hands up now?
You got me.
Weapon.
Why would you come back?
I thought your brother
was the dumb one.
My brother's a lot of
things. but he's not dumb.
You know what?
Thank you. Mason.
What is it exactly that I
haven't figured out yet?
Sean. do the honors.
You ever heard of 4D chess?
Oh. Jesus Christ.
Mason wasn't the only one
in those crates.
So Anton and the new
guy are here somewhere.
Perfect.
Manme will find them.
and you can all die together.
Sweet Link.
Let's get this shit.
Hey. hey. you just make
sure you hold on right there.
Let's get the fuck out
of here now.
So what?
So now you steal my car?
I'm supposed to be impressed.
They have dozens of them.
Yeah. well. auto theft.
it's not our strong suit.
You.
You're part of this.
Who. me?
Yeah.
Oh. shit.
I knew I was forgetting
something.
No. you're doing good.
You're good.
I mean. didn't you wonder how Mason
was able to start that boat so quickly?
Hey. cute little place
you got here. Abel.
My humble abode.
Where's the restroom?
Right down the hall on the left.
Thank you.
I'll wait
for you in the break room.
All right.
I don't understand boats.
but that does sound like
something that should
have occurred to you. Abel.
I'm just saying.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
And while all that was happening.
I was sneaking out of the yacht.
All stealthy.
Like a badass.
Like a ninja.
And not that you would
care. Salazar. but don't worry.
Link made sure the whole crew
was safe before we blew up the yacht.
She made a little
call this morning.
Yes. Captain.
This is Suzanne Connors from
Custom Yachts Incorporated.
I'm afraid we've got a little problem with
a carbon monoxide leak on your vessel.
You need to evacuate
the crew immediately.
Yeah. I understand.
Our technicians are on the
way to fix the issue right now.
And did you see that explosion?
It was our best distraction ever. giving
Mason the chance to sneak back here.
And giving me a chance
to finally blow his brains out.
May I tell you something?
Now.
I don't know a lot about art.
I really don't.
But I really kind
of like this painting.
Kind of like it?
Yes.
It is worth over $100
million. you fucking idiot.
That's my point. you see.
But I do know someone
who knows a lot about art.
And they say. well. they
say that... Ah. ah. ah.
Back off.
Okay. let me tell you
from a distance then. okay?
If you go to your painting and
you look closely. okay. you'll see
that the paint strokes are perfect.
but they're too perfect. okay?
There should be little
cracks in the paint stroke.
Do you see that?
There's not.
In the oil paint.
So I think you've got
a forger on your hands.
Yeah.
Oh. and you know. before
Anton and Victor stole your car.
They swapped the paintings out.
Sweet Link!
Hundred mil!
Whoo!
Now you all fucking die.
Uh-oh.
You know what?
I know I forgot one last thing.
Can I offer you champagne?
Well. I never say no to bubbly.
Nectar. Odessa is here.
Motherfucker.
Checkmate?
Nope.
Not quite.
Almost.
Hello. Abel.
It's nice to see you again.
Why don't you put
that on the floor?
Now?
Now.
Checkmate. Salazar.
Oh. for fuck's sake. get me
away from these people. please.
Please!
So you're like
the mastermind now?
I can't keep track of you.
It looks like my old pal Abel Salazar
is out of the picture once again.
Creating quite the power vacuum.
Sounds like a business
opportunity for someone like you.
Opportunity for us.
You knew he was still alive
this whole time. didn't you?
Mason. you never said anything
about blowing up the yachts.
A yacht blew up?
Yikes.
Sounds dangerous.
Yeah. well.
you're lucky nobody got killed.
Our deal would have been off.
Why don't you try keeping
him behind bars this time?
Do I look like a prison warden
to you?
My job's just to catch him.
Well then. well done.
Thanks.
Do me a favor.
Keep that brother of
yours out of trouble. please.
Oh. I can't guarantee that.
I'd hate to have to put
him behind bars one day.
You know I will if I have to.
Hmm.
But can you keep him there?
Ah.
Let's go.
I never underestimated
Mason Goddard.
But Abel Salazar sure did.
You know who else Abel
Salazar underestimated?
Hamish Hawks.
Oh. my God.
Look at this.
We're almost full of surprises.
What was that?
I don't know.
But what I do know
is we are something.
We pulled it off.
Yeah.
That was so fun.
Wasn't it fun?
Well. yeah.
I forgot how exciting
the whole thing can be.
Yeah. well. you're not thinking of
getting back into the game. are you?
No. I don't know about that.
I might have had enough
excitement for now. at least.
Well. that's good.
because I need an art expert
to help me sell that
$100 million painting.
Oh. my commission is
steep and non-negotiable.
Yeah. well.
you're gonna earn every penny.
Did it. guys?
God. Sean.
How fucking cool was that?
It was so cool.
Oh. man. yeah.
It's all you. buddy.
And I have to apologize for not buying into
this whole 4D chess thing. and I was wrong.
Really?
Yeah. I was wrong.
Well. that's awesome. man.
because I got this other idea.
Don't push it.
No. no. no. I'm telling you. it's
the greatest idea for a heist ever.
Wait. I want to hear it.
Well. don't encourage him.
No. I want to hear it.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm